# **Jagriti Jain**

🕜 Vishakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh, India | 🖂 jagriti262@gmail.com | 🖠 7566900093

inwww.linkedin.com/in/jagriti-jain-4334581b7

## **About Me**

Seasoned and resourceful Industry professional, offering 11+ years of successful experience and insightful experience, in supply chain management, branch administration, efficiently managing orders and logistics of high business turnovers, organizing CSR activities, safety events & employee engagement activities for team bonding and motivation. Exploring challenging leadership assignment to leverage multifaceted competences and deliver outstanding results aligned to organizational goals and objectives thus, driving the organization to next level of excellence.

# **Leadership Strengths**

- Competent professional with multifunctional experience across supply chain management, sourcing and procurement, vendor management, cost planning and management, warehousing and inventory management, vendor management, commercial management, materials management, and staff management.
- Specialized in driving and delivering supply chain strategy road map by focusing on people, process, and technology with continuous improvement.
- Skilled in efficiently handling B2B, B2C and e-commerce base complex data analysis (Inventory/ Sales/ Manpower) & presentation with strong negotiation & cross functional skills.
- Skilled in driving business process improvements to improve operational efficiencies rationalize and optimize costs and ensure smooth flawless supply chain operations.
- Experienced in restructuring supply chain function, adopting international industry best practices aligned to corporate goals and objectives.
- Deft in building and sustaining productive stakeholder relations as well as leading and motivating multinational cross-functional professional teams eliciting superior win-win outcomes.
- Proactive, achievement driven professional with excellent communicating, coordinating, problem solving, decision making, planning and execution skills.

# **Excellence Sphere**

- Supply Chain Management
- Operations Management
- Order Management
- Branch Administration
- MIS Analysis
- Logistics Management
- Inventory Management
- Sourcing & Procurement

- Internal/ External Audits
- Material Management
- Vendor Management
- Process Automation
- Productivity Improvement
- Customer Relations
- HR Administration
- Employee Engagement

- Performance Management
- ERP Implementation
- Business Analysis/ Data Analysis
- Functional Training & Development
- Operational Excellence
- Strategic Planning & Execution
- Liaison & Coordination
- Team Building & Leadership

# **Professional Experience**

Godrej & Boyce Mfg. Co. Ltd., Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

Sep 2011 – Dec 2022 (11 Years, 4 months)

#### Career Path:

| Deputy Manager (Customer Support Team Lead) – Commercial | Sep 2018 - Dec 2022 |
|--|---------------------|
| Assistant Manager – Commercial                           | Sep 2015 - Aug 2018 |
| Senior Executive – Commercial                            | Sep 2012 - Aug 2015 |
| Graduate Trainee – Commercial                            | Sep 2011 - Aug 2012 |

### **Notable Achievements:**

| • | Regional Award for Best Admin Team – West Zone - Raipur Branch            | 2011 - 2012 |
|---|---|-------------|
| • | Regional Award for Best Customer Support Team – West Zone - Raipur Branch | 2011 - 2012 |
| • | Regional Award for Best Customer Support Team – West Zone - Raipur Branch | 2016 - 2017 |
| • | Best Team Customer Support Second Runners Up – Raipur Branch (All India)  | 2021 - 2022 |
| • | Best Commercial Branch – Kaizen Second Runners up - Raipur Branch         | 2015 - 2016 |
| • | Individual Award: Best Branch Customer Support Employee                   | 2013 - 2014 |
| • | Individual Award: Promising Employee of the Branch                        | 2014 - 2015 |
| • | Individual Award: Top 10 Employees for scoring highest points in Kaizen   | 2021 - 2022 |
|   |   |             |

#### **Key Deliverables:**

- Played a key role in shifting of order processing cell to Mumbai for Raipur Nagpur from Nov 2022 to Dec 2022.
- Involved in the implementation of automated MIS for Sales/ Service Team of West Zone for Pending Order, Stock, Billed Sales and Outstanding.
- Directed and coordinated global supply chain functions through strategy, resource optimization, profitability maximization, and KPIs resulting in the maximization of customer satisfaction.
- Drove continual initiatives for improving supply chain processes, adopting industry best practices to eliminate existing pain points in coordination with all stakeholders.
- Planned, organized, directed, managed, and evaluated the material management activities.
- Made significant contributions to the implementation of ERP Infor LN in branch & training of team members.
- Billed Sales Projection for Godrej Interio on monthly basis for pending order/ inventory.
- Assisted the sales, service, warehouse, and head office teams with MIS as and when required for review and analysis.
- Monitored all deliveries of finished goods and services from production/ warehouse to outlets/ customers.
- Managed all logistics matters and ensured safe receipt, storage, retrieval, and timely dispatch of goods.
- Actively participated in ISO/ Internal Audits for branch; compiled and published Kaizen Dashboard for West Zone.
- Involved in order booking process for Interio (furniture), Appliances (White goods), Locks (Hardware) and Security Solutions.
- Efficiently handled B2B (Banking, Key Accounts of Govt, PSUs), B2C (retail) and eCommerce customers queries and resolution.
- Contributed to smooth dispatches and cost-effective planning, by working in unison with warehouse team.
- Developed resourceful & reliable vendor base with efficient performance management and robust pre-qualification processes.
- Maintained productive relationships with all vendors and managed vendor performance ensuring smooth supply chain operations.
- Managed liquidation of excess stock, old stock via inter-branch transfers and sales via dealers.

## **Education**

MBA - Operation Management, Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning

Apr 2014 - June 2017 2008 - 2011

Bachelors of Computer Applications, Disha College, Raipur

## **Personal Details**

Date of Birth: 26 Jan 1990Nationality: Indian

Marital Status: Married

Languages Known: English, Hindi